# RAÚL CASSONE

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

+34 653 62 69 27



irpcassone@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ra%C3 %BAl-cassone-07452a195/

## PROFILE

After years in the world of music and sound, I decided to pivot my career, embarking on a journey into Full-Stack development, specializing in the MERN stack. Committed to delivering exceptional results through clean and maintainable code, robust applications, and effective collaboration in multidisciplinary teams.

## SKILLS

- Node.js
- React Redux
- Eslint
- Next.js
- Postman

- Git
- Styled Components
- Jest
- Vitest
- JWT

- TypeScript
- BEM
- React Testing Library
- MongoDB
- MSW

- Figma
- HTML5
- Tailwind CSS
- SuperTest
- Github Actions

## EDUCATION

# **Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp**

ISDI coders 2022

# **Sound Certificate of Higher Education**

CEF Mallorca 2012 - 2014

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Web development rebranding Dublab Barcelona

Freelance frontend web development | October 2023 - January 2024

- Next.JS, Django, Tailwind CSS, Typescript
- Complete redesign of the frontend side
- Rearrangement of existing functionalities
- Implementation of new features: weekly calendar from third-party API, new endpoint to manage latest content added from the CMS.
- Integration of different APIs for proper display of page content
- Coordination with backend programmer for the proper implementation of new features and bug correction.

# Web Full-Stack - Barcelona Reverbera

Freelance Full-Stack web development MERN • Septiembre 2023 - Octubre 2023

- Responsive front-end development using REACT, with prior wireframing in Figma
- Back-end development using ExpressJS and MongoDB
- 90% test coverage across the entire project

#### **Picnic Sound Studio**

Freelance in Music and Postproduction | 2022 - 2023

- Creation and development of the project, establishing work dynamics and protocols
- Creation of original music and sound effects for advertising campaigns and artistic projects
- Project management and budget negotiation

# **Dublab Barcelona Radio**

Studio Manager and Technical Lead | 2021 - 2023

- As the studio manager, I was responsible for coordinating the daily schedule, managing hourly distribution, and producing monthly programs and guests, both in Spanish and English.
- As the technical lead, I was responsible for live and recorded broadcasts and the management of resulting files.
- Organization of complementary activities for the radio: events, content for social media, interviews, technical assistance, etc.
- Coordination and training of volunteers
- Participation in content direction and platform functionality

#### LANGUAGES

• **Spanish** - Native

• Catalán - Native

• English - Fluent